(laughing):
My goodness!
(Sheldon:)Do you remember
“comes with apsparagus”?
(Sheldon:)Howard and Bernadette,
(Sheldon:)you tried to comfort me
when I was ill,
(Sheldon:)and I treated you terribly.
(Sheldon:)I'm sorry.
(Howard:)Wow.
(chuckles)
(Howard:)I'm impressed.
(Sheldon:)No, no, no, wait.
(Sheldon:)I'm not done.
(Sheldon:)Allow me to underscore
my sentiment
(Sheldon:)with a haunting rendition
of Brenda Lee's “I'm Sorry”
(Sheldon:)played on the pan flute.
Apology accepted!
Forgiven, forgiven!
(Sheldon:)All right, that's eight hours
of practice down the drain.
And to memorialize
this occasion,
(Sheldon:)here are your
commemorative T-shirts.
“Sheldon Cooper
apologized to me”"
“And he made it
all better.”